favorwarehouse.com 2015-12-30

# Privacy Policy | FavorWarehouse

Favor Warehouse is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers and using information responsibly. Our security and privacy policies are detailed below.

## How we use information

Our site stores personal information we collect in during the transaction process in order process the transaction and execute your order. Limited information from the order for including contact information (name, address, telephone number, email address, etc.) from the order form is used to process your orders and communicate order status including shipment tracking information.

Your contact information is also used to get in touch with you when necessary either directly or via our shipping partners including UPS, USPS and FedEx. 

Financial information (credit card numbers, credit card expiration dates, billing address, etc.) that is collected is used strictly to bill you for products and services. Information collected on any of our forms may be used to contact you, whether by telephone, live chat or via emails in response to your inquiries. From time to time Favor Warehouse may also contact you via email to inform you of new product releases and promotions - our email marketing contacts provide a means for you to opt-out of further promotional emails.

## Cookies

Cookies are transferred from our servers to your computer via your Web browser. They make it possible for us to store your shopping cart details until you are ready to check out. They also allow our servers to recognize your browser on subsequent visits.

## How we collect information

This site uses a secure server (SSL) certified by GeoTrust? to encrypt all of your personal information. We employ strict security measures and information access controls to safeguard your personal information.

## Customer agreement

By using our web site or purchasing a product from us, you agree to the collection and use of information as set forth in this privacy policy. Any updates to our information security and privacy policies will be posted to this page.

## Commitment to customer service

Favor Warehouse is committed to our customers’ satisfaction and creating a great customer experience. You can contact our customer care department via email at info@favorwarehouse.com or at 914-514-3244.

## Authorized third parties

We use third-party service providers including but not limited to Google, MSN, Yahoo and Amazon to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. These providers may collect anonymous information about your visits to our site and may use this information to serve you advertisements for other goods and services.

They may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to serve targeted advertisements for other goods and services. No personally identifiable information is used in this process.

We also work with a third party to monitor site performance and identify opportunities to improve our products and services. We do not share personally identifiable information with these third parties.

We use data from Google's Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender and interests) with Google Analytics.

Data collected through the use of interest based audience data with Google Analytics is used to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your browsing history.

None of the date collected by us or through the use of any third party ever collects personally identifiable information under any circumstances.

  * Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).
  * You can also opt-out of Analytics Data collection by any site you visit by using the following browser add-on from Google: [Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).
